City of Newburgh Urban Renewal; Collection apap375
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Administrative, 1945-2000; 1
  - Leonard Sarinsky, 1972; 1975 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Lewis Candy Store, 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Lewis Gayle, 1962-1965 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Liberty Street Facade Improvement, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Liberty Street Facade Improvement, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Liberty Street Facade Improvement 110 Liberty Street, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Liberty Street Facade Improvement 90 Washington Street, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Liberty Street Plaza at Public Safety Buildings, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Lillian King Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1966-1967 (Box 64, Folder 25)
  - Lillian Watson 181 Water Street, 1967-1968 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Lillian Watson, Watson's Liquor Store Relocation Payment, 1967-1968 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Lillie Brandon Conley, 1963-1965 (Box 64, Folder 33)
  - Lillie Brandon Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1963-1965 (Box 64, Folder 38)
  - Lindsley Schepmoes, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Lloyd Boykin 238 Water Street, 1961-1963 (Box 64, Folder 40)
  - Lloyd Boykin Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1965-1966 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Loan and Grant Amendatory NYR-12, 1968-1970; 1972-1973; Undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Local Partnership Toolkit, 1995 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Losses and Charge-Offs, 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 70)
  - Lot 8 Alexander Kafka, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Lot H, 1974-1977 (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - Loth Estate, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Loth's Liquor Store, 1961-1962 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Louise Beauty Shop, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Louise Lawson Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Lydia Simmons, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Lynn Keller, 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - MacDonald Feed Store, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Mack Butler, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - MacMillen Hearings, 1963; 1968 (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - Mail: General, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Mamie Smith Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Mancini, 1969-1970 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Mandel: Grand Street School 77-79 Broadway, 1982 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Mandel-Hudson Hill Homes (1 of 2), 1984-1986 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Mandel-Hudson Hill Homes (2 of 2), 1984-1986 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Map of Varick Homes Site Improvements- June 1981 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Maple 200, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Maps, 1971-1972 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Maps and Surveys, 1986; Undated (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Maps- Ritangelo, 1973 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Marcus, 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Marins Drive Acquisitions, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Marion E Donahue and Edward Flanagan, 1970-1972 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Martin, 1967-1968 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Martin Commissioners, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Martin DeVito Parcel #10 Lake Street, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Mary VM Zint, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Master Planning including 701 Project, 1959; 1962; 1964-1966 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Mathew and Katherine Kehoe, 1970-1971 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Matthew Kehoe, 1971-1972 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Mattie Williams 6-8 Montgomery Street, 2-4-1, Lot 13, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Maurer Development Inc, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Maurer Development Inc, Disposition Parcels, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Max Levinson 120 Water Street, 1961-1962; 1967 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Max Levinson Inventory, 1957; 1964-1967 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Max Levinson, cont'd, 1965-1967 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Max Levinson, Newburgh Tissue Co. Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1964-1967 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - McDermott and Flanagan, 1972-1973 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - McGill, Williams, 1952; 1972; 1980-1985 (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - McIntyre, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - McKinney's Consolidated Laws of New York Book 9A, 1950 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - McKneally, George, 1968-1971 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - McMillen, William Gees Awings, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Median, 1973-1974 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Melvin Allen, Allen's Tobacco Store Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Memorandum, 1963-1964 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Menley, Horowitz, Robinson, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Merrill and Ida Robinson, 1963; 1967-1968 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Merrill Robinson, Robinson Lounge, Parcel 3-1-11, 1967-1969 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Mesh Realty Co., 1967-1969 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Mesh Realty Corp, Samuel and Ann Mandel, 97 Grand Street, 1988; Undated (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Metro Plans Proposed for Newburgh, 1965-1970; 1973 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - MEWS, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - MEWS, cont'd, 1971-1973; 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Michael and Quinn, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 54)
  - Michael F Quinn, Contract #57, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 96)
  - Michael Fuentes, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Michael Stein, 43-47 Washington Terrace, 1972-1975 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Mid Hudson Electric Newburgh Urban Renewal, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Midstate Elevator Co. Inc., 1986 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Mills Arlether, 1962; 1965 (Box 64, Folder 24)
  - Miner F and Marie McMillen, 88-90 Lake St, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Mini Loan Correspondence, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Minutes, 1967-1968 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Minutes of Agency Meetings, 1975-1976 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Miron Lumber Co., 1974-1977 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Misc. Contracts, 1971-1972; 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Misc. Urban Renewal, 1959; 1971-1973 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous, 1961-1964 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Moderate Facade Rehabilitation 118 and 126 Broadway, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Moderate Facade Rehabilitation 129 and 150 Lander, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Montgomery St. Rehab and Retaining Wall, Bid December 1, 1969, 1969-1970 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Montgomery St. Retaining Wall Data, 1968-1969 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Montgomery St. Widening Valente and Sullivan Inc., 1968-1970 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Montgomery Street Improvements Contract Bids + Pre-Constr. Conf., 1979 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Montgomery Street Misc., 1979-1980 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Moulton, 1967 (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - MR Construction Co, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - Myrtle McGill, 1972; 1987 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - NAACP, 1967; 1974 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Nathan Pollack, 1972-1973; 1978 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - NDP 2nd Year Closeout, 1971-1975 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - NDP Areas 1,2,3,4,5, Preliminary, Raymond, Parish and Pine 1 of 2, 1969 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - NDP Areas 1,2,3,4,5, Preliminary, Raymond, Parish and Pine 2 of 2, 1969 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - NDP NY A10 Lake Street Parcel No. 5 Lac Pac Realty Corp, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - NDP NY A10 Lake Street Parcel No. 7 Lac Pac Realty Corp, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - NDP NY A10 Lake Street Parcels 13 and 14 Kathryne Thorpe, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - NDP NYA 10 Lake Street Parcel 26 Herman Zaransky and Luke Stein, 1971 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - NDP, Raymond, May, Parish and Pine, NYA-10, 1969-1970 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Neighborhood Dev Program, 1969-1974 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Neighborhood Development Program, 1969-1972 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Neighborhood Development Program, 1970-1973 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Neighborhood Development Program NDP Areas 2 and 3, 1969-1970; Undated (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Newburgh Area Industrial Developers, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Newburgh Bleachery, 192-194 Lake Street, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Newburgh Building and Lot Information, 1961 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Newburgh City Hall Complex, 1973 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Newburgh Economic Development, 1982-1984 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Newburgh Housing Associates, 1972-1976 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Newburgh Housing Authority, 1982; 1985-1986 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Newburgh Housing Authority Midstate Elevator Co., 1986 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Newburgh Leasing Corp., 1973 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Newburgh NCMD Contracts, Reports, and Invoices, 1982-1983 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Newburgh Plumbing and Heating Supplies, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Newburgh Preservation Association Grant Application, 1983 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Newburgh Urban Renewal Agency Folder #2, 1977-1979; 1981-1983; 1987 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Newburgh Urban Renewal Agency NDP A10 Lake Street, 1970 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Newburgh Urban Renewal Agency NDP A10 Lake Street Book #1, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Newburgh Urban Renewal Agency NDP NYA10 Lake Street Book #2, 1970 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Newburgh Urban Renewal Agency Report of Examination 68M-339, 1965-1968 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Newburgh Urban Renewal Agency Sales Brochure, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Newburgh Urban Renewal Agency v Watson, 1967 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Newburgh Urban Renewal Agency vs Watson Minutes, 1967 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Newburgh Works III, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Newburgh Zoning Board Green and White Spiral Notebook, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Newspaper Articles 1966-1967 (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - Newspaper Articles 1970 (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - Newspaper Articles 1971 (Box 58, Folder 21)
  - Newspaper Articles 1972 (Box 58, Folder 22)
  - Newspaper Articles July 1973 (Box 58, Folder 25)
  - Newspaper Articles August 1973 (Box 58, Folder 24)
  - Newspaper Articles September 1973 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper Articles October 1973 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper Articles November 1973 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper Articles December 1973 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper Articles 1973 (Box 58, Folder 23)
  - Newspaper Articles January 1974 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper Articles February 1974 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper Articles March 1974 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper Articles April 1974 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper Articles May 1974 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper Articles June 1974 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper Articles July 1974 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Newspaper Articles August 1974 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Newspaper Articles September 1974 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Newspaper Articles October 1974 (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Newspaper Articles November 1974 (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Newspaper Articles December 1974 (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - Nick and Rosalie Roscino (1 of 2), 1971 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Nick and Rosalie Roscino (2 of 2), 1971 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Norwood B. Herring, TINY'S, Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1964-1965 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Note of Issue For Motion, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 55)
  - Notes and Bounds, 1963; 1968-1969; 1971; Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Notice of Pendency of Action, Undated (Box 17, Folder 54)
  - Notification to City of Sale NURA Properties, 1974-1977 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - November 1973 Relocation, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - NURA 1965 Legislation Creation and Justification, 1965-1967 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - NURA 1967 Photograph of Board Members (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - NURA Cash Receipts, etc., 1962-1974 (Item 3)
  - NURA Contract Documents and Specifications, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - NURA Dispo Parcel 5B, 1983-1984; 1988 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - NURA Expenditures, 1966-1978 (Item 1)
  - NURA Lawsuits, Accident Lawsuits, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - NURA Meetings 1965 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - NURA Meetings 1966 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - NURA Meetings 1967 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - NURA Meetings 1968, 1968-1969 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - NURA Meetings 1969, 1969-1970 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - NURA Personnel Attendance Record 1968-1982 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - NURA Project Notes First Series 1974, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - NURA Project NYA-10 Expenditures Acct., 1971-1973 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - NURA Property to City Leases, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - NURA Revolving Fund, Cash Disbursement, 1966-1976 (Item 2)
  - NURA Rough Grading Disposition Parcels, 1975 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - NURA Rough Grading Disposition Parcels Pt. 2, 1975 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - NURA Rough Grading Disposition Parcels Pt. 3, 1975 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - NURA Rough Grading Disposition Parcels Pt. 4, 1975 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - NURA State Urban Renewal Fund, 1971-1975 (Item 4)
  - NURA Tax Record Book, 1964-1965; 1970-1973 (Item 5)
  - NURA to City Muchattoes Lake Area, 1970-1973; 1974-1976 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - NURA Urban Renewal Volume III Minutes and Resolutions, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - NURA Vol II Minutes January 1968 to December 1969, 1968-1969 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - NURA/UDC Land Disposition Agreement 1970 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - NURA: Members, Meetings, Corresp., 1968-1972; 1973; 1976 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - NY SUR 19 Application for Second Amendatory, 1970-1971 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - NY Telephone, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - NY Telephone Undergrounding and rights of way, 1970; 1973; 1977 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - NYA 10 Acquisition, 1970-1973 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - NYA 10 Acquisition, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 44)
  - NYA 10 Closeout Documents, 1971; 1973; 1977 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - NYA 10 Condemnation, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - NYA 10 County Asphalt Payroll-RESTRICTED, 1973 (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - NYA 10 Data, 1975-1976 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - NYA 10 Deeds, Titles, Etc., 1970-1972; Undated (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - NYA 10 Expend Budget, 1971-1974 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - NYA 10 Financing Plan, 1971-1974 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - NYA 10 First Year Close Out, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - NYA 10 Parcel #3, 1973-1975 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - NYR 12 Amendment to Original Plan, 1962; 1969-1970 (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - NYR 12 Appraisal and Acquisition Correspondence, 1961; 1968 (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - NYR 12 Closeout and History Summary, 1970-1973; 1979 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - NYR 12 Closeout Law, 1967; 1969-1972; Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Includes 1970 Newburgh Urban Renewal Agency Annual Report.
  - NYR 12 Contr. 2 Demolition Map, List, and License Agreements, Undated (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - NYR 12 Correspondence with Housing and Home Finance Agency, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - NYR 12 Deeds- Originals, 1962-1964 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - NYR 12 Eligibility and Relocation Report, 1958 (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - NYR 12 Final Project Report, 1959 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - NYR 12 Financing Plan, 1961; 1968; 1970; 1974; Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - NYR 12 History, NYR-189 Summary, Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - NYR 12 (LG), 1968-1971 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - NYR 12 LG Amendatory Unnumbered, 1970-1971 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - NYR 12 Report on Plan, Nov. 1960 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - NYR 12 State Fund Bank Reconciliation, 1973-1974 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - NYR 189 Amended Application to HUD 1973 (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - NYR 189 Amendment to Original Plan, 1969-1973 (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - NYR 189 Approved Condemnation Resolutions, 1970-1973 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - NYR 189 Audits, HUD, 1975; 1978 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - NYR 189 Closeout Documents and Summaries and Public Safety Bldg, 1976-1980 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - NYR 189 Expense and General Ledger, 1967-1969; 1973-1975 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - NYR 189 HUD Concurrence for Condemnations, 1970-1974 (Box 30, Folder 38)
  - NYR 189 January 1977 to June 1977, 1975-1977 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - NYR 189 Land Use and Economic Analysis, 1968; 1974; Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - NYR 189 Mandel, 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - NYR 189 Part II Application for Loan Grant, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - NYR 189 PJ Enterprises, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - NYR 189 Project Expenditure Budget and Documents, 1969-1974 (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - NYR 189 Project Notes, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - NYR 189 Receipts Account, 1966-1967; 1969 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - NYR 189 Rough Grading, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - NYR 189 Rough Grading Contract Documents and Specs., 1974 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - NYR 189 Tax Map Listings/ Owners, 1961 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - NYR 189 Vouchers, 1980; 1982 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - NYR 189 Water Street Title Reports and Parcel Maps, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - NYS CAP Grant Contract, 1964; 1970-1972 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - NYSHPO Correspondence, 1980; 1984-1986 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - NYSUR 100 Parcel 2, 1, 1, 1967-1973 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Offers, 1966-1967 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Office of Economic Development Correspondence, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Office of NYS Parks Correspondence, 1986 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Office Supplies 83.9E, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Old Urban Renewal and Interstate Industrial Project I-1, 1961-1963; 1966 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Old Water Dept. File from Carter Street, 1966-1970; 1974-1977; 1980-1981; 2000 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    Includes 1968 Newburgh Urban Renewal Agency Annual Report.
  - O'Neill, Edward, 1965-1968 (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - Options, 1963-1966 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Order of Immediate Possession and Appointment, 1971-1973 (Box 17, Folder 56)
  - Otie Tallie, 1964-1965 (Box 64, Folder 49)
  - Owner Lists NYR 189 Parcels 2, 3, + 4, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Palatine, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - Parcel #8 118-136 Lake, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Parcel 10, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Parcel 11A, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Parcel 11C, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Parcel 12A Title Report, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Parcel 12B Title Report, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Parcel 13 PJ Enterprises, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Parcel 14 Title Report, 1970; 1986 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Parcel 22 NYR 189 Chestnut Partners, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Parcel 23 Title Report, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Parcel 32 Title Report, 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Parcel 4 Thomas W. Chadwick, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Parcel 5C Title Report NYR 189, 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Parcel 6 Peter Olympia, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Parcel 9A Title Report, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Parcel 9B Title Report, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Parcel Descriptions, 1972-1977 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Parcel Four-One-Three, 1961 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Parcel Four-Two-Two, 1961 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Parcel Surveys, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Parcels 10, 11A, 11B, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Parcels 3 and 4 NYR 12 Oak Partners, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Parcels 3 and 4 Title Report, 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Parcels 5A to 5B, 1986; 1999 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Parcels 6 + 6A Title Report, 1987; 1990 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Parcels NYR-12 and Square Footage, Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Parcels on Water St between Bourne Apts + Broad St, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Parkhill Harris and Josephine Magliato, 1970-1971 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Part 1 of Amendatory Application and Loan Grant, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Part I Application for Capital Grant, 1959 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Payment Receipts, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Payment Vouchers, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Payments in Lieu of Taxes, 1968-1973 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Payroll Forms-RESTRICTED, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Payroll Journal, 1974 (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - Payroll Register 1967-1971 Urban Renewal and Property Mgmt-RESTRICTED (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - People City, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Period October 1, 1972 to December 31, 1972, 1972-1974 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Peterson's Garage, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Petition Page 1 Blank Form, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 53)
  - Pinky and Gardner Williams 348 Water Street, 1964; 1970 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - PJ Enterprises, 1971-1972 (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - Plaintiffs Exhibits, 1967 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Planning Advance Contract, 1958; 1961 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Planning Board, 1968-1969 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Planning Board Minutes, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Planning Board Minutes 1965 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - PLK/M, 3 and 4 NYR-12, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - PLM/OAK NYR 189 Partners, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - PLM/OAK Partners NYR-189, 1971; 1985 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Postage 83.14E, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Poughkeepsie Wrecking NYA-10, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - The Price and Lee Co., 1969; 1971 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Proclaimer Certificates Acquisition, 1971-1975 (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Program Income, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Progress Report to City Council, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 71)
  - Progress Reports, 1968; 1970-1973 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Progress Reports Submitted to City Council, 1957-1958 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Project Council 1962 Correspondence Gilbert Rashbaum (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Project Loan Notes, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Project Loan Notes - 189 (1976), 1974-1976; Undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Project Loan Notes - 189 (3/1976-3/1977), 1975-1976; Undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Project Loan Notes - NYA-10 (Dec. 17, 1974-Dec. 1975), Undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Project Notes, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Project Notes (March 1977-), Undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Project Notes First Series 1970, 1970-1971 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Property Management, 1969-1970; Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Property of Hyman and Ruth Knopf, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Property of Lorea Medley, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Property Transfer, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Proposal Glenn Hines Storm King Contracting, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Public Safety Building, 1973 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Public Safety Building Correspondence on Demolition and Acquisition, 1973-1977; Undated (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Public Safety Building Non-Cash 6202, 1971-1975 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Quarterly Report of Planning Cost, 1956-1960 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Quentin Skipwith, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - Quinn Contract with Appraiser, 1970-1973; 1978 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Ratz, 1970-1972 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Ray Bedard Rehab, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 61)
  - Raymond, Parish, and Pine, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 53)
  - Reading File, June 1969 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Reading File, July 1969 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Reading File, August 1969 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Reading File, September 1969 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Reading File, October 1969 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Reading File, November 1969 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Reading File, December 1969 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Reading File, January 1970 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Reading File, February 1970 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Reading File, March 1970 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Reading File, April 1970 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Reading File, May 1970 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Reading File, June 1970 (Box 41, Folder 31)
  - Reading File, July 1970 (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - Reading File, August 1970 (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - Reading File, October 1970 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Reading File, September 1970 (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - Reading File, November 1970 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - Reading File, December 1970 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Reading File, January 1971 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Reading File, February 1971 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Reading File, March 1971 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Reading File, April 1971 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Reading File, May 1971 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Reading File, June 1971 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Reading File, July 1971 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Reading File, August 1971 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Reading File, September 1971 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Reading File, October 1971 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Reading File, November 1971 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Reading File, December 1971 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Reading File, January 1972 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Reading File, February 1972 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Reading File, March 1972 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Reading File, April 1972 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Reading File, May 1972 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Reading File, June 1972 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Reading File, July 1972 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Reading File, August 1972 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Reading File, September 1972 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Reading File, October 1972 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Reading File, November 1972 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Reading File, December 1972 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Reading File, January 1973 (Box 24, Folder 58)
  - Reading File, February 1973 (Box 24, Folder 57)
  - Reading File, March 1973 (Box 24, Folder 56)
  - Reading File, April 1973 (Box 24, Folder 55)
  - Reading File, May 1973 (Box 24, Folder 54)